So you have to
所以你要在
Within the shortest time
最短的时间内
Raise your performance
把自己的业绩提上来
Prove that we
证明咱们
Worthy of this spot
配得上这个名额
Talk about it
说来说去
Isn't it just developing customers
不就是开发客户吗
That's right
说得没错
Sister Xiaoning
那筱柠姐
You have to hold on a little tighter
你可给抓点紧了
From developing customers to lending
从开发客户到放款
There is also a very
还有一个非常
A long process
漫长的过程
Manager Zhao
赵经理
What do you do
干什么
You put that client of yours
你把你的那个客户
Give us a few small paints
给我们小涂几个
Isn't this performance coming up
这业绩不就上来了吗
Your abacus
你这算盘
It's all hitting me in the face
都打到我脸上来了
You are her master
你是她师父
Why don't you give it
你怎么不给啊
Don't you know me
你还不知道我吗
Where's my client
我的客户呢
They are all relatively large amounts
都是金额比较大的
Not very suitable
不太适合
Our current Xiaotu
我们现阶段的小涂
Unlike our manager Zhao
不像咱们赵经理
Where's your client
你的客户呢
All Pratt & Whitney customers
都是普惠客户
Then just give a few of them
那随便给几个就够了
Also
还有啊
Who usually
谁平时
In the office it's always
在办公室里边老是
Come
来
Call me Brother Zhao
叫我小赵哥
Let us at every turn
动不动就让我们
Little Brother Zhao, Little Brother Zhao shouted
小赵哥 小赵哥的叫着
What about now
现在呢
backed out
打退堂鼓了
flinched
退缩了
Quit
不干了
Not like our manager Zhao
不像我们赵经理为人啊
Xiao Tu
小涂
Little Brother Zhao
小 小赵哥
I've already prepared it for you
早就给你准备好了
You see, I'll just say it
你看我就说吧
Here's what I've done earlier correctly
这是我之前对过的
Basic materials of three companies
三家企业的基本材料
The financing plan is around five million
融资方案在五百万左右
Take it and try it
拿去试试
Is this not so good
这不太好吧
What's so bad about this
这有什么不好的
Why don't you quickly thank you, Brother Zhao
还不快谢谢你小赵哥
Thank you, Brother Zhao
谢谢小赵哥
Actually, I recently
其实我最近
Also contacted a company
也联系了一家公司
shipyard's
造船厂的
It's just the beginning
就是刚开始
Still don't know what's going on
还不知道到底什么情况
This is like this
这个是这样啊
As long as the other party's qualifications are not bad
只要对方资质还不错
Let's work hard and fight for it
咱们就加油争取呗
By the way
对了
Be a customer
做客户
It's the same as asking for a debt
就跟要债是一样的
Don't expect the other party to take the initiative
你别指望对方主动噢
We have to take the initiative ourselves
我们自己得主动出击噢
Good
好
check
查收
Interest
利息
Thirty-two
三十二
Mosquito meat is also meat
蚊子肉也是肉
Keep
收着
Why are you looking at me
看着我干吗
I haven't officially congratulated you yet
还没正式恭喜你
The written test went smoothly
笔试顺利
Congratulations to Xiao Tu
恭喜小涂同学
Thank you
谢谢
There are no weak soldiers under a strong general
强将底下无弱兵
Main
主要
Can't embarrass Mr. Ji
是不能给纪总丢脸
Is it just Mr. Ji
只是纪总吗
What else could there be
那还能有什么
What do you want to do
你想干吗
That Mr. Ji and Xiao Tu
那纪总跟小涂
What else can I do
还能干什么
Thank you Mr. Ji for your encouragement
谢谢纪总的鼓励
I went to work
我上班去了
During this time of preparing for the exam
备考这段时间
Thank you for your hard work
辛苦大家了
Buy coffee for everyone
给大家买咖啡
Thank you
感谢一下
Thank you Xiao Tu
谢谢小涂
Thank you Thank you
谢谢 谢谢 谢谢
Xiao Tang
小唐
I don't drink this flavor
我不喝这个口味
Thank you
谢谢啊
Xiao Tu
小涂
I'm sleepy right now
我这会儿正好犯困呢
You can drink two drinks in one go
可以一 口气连干两杯
OK
好呀
Thank you
谢谢
By the way
对了
Did you buy it for the leader
你给领导买了吗
And a cup of Aurui White
还有一杯澳瑞白
Good
好
Senior brother doesn't drink Aorui Bai
师哥不喝澳瑞白
In addition to American style
他除了美式
Don't touch anything
什么都不碰
Mr. Ji
纪总
Do you have mine
有我的吗
I'm sorry
不好意思啊
Only one cup of Aurui White left
就剩一杯澳瑞白了
Give it to me
给我吧
It's okay
没关系
Not senior brother
不是师哥
That cup is Auris white
那杯是澳瑞白
It tastes pretty good
还挺好喝
Thank you
谢谢啊
You're welcome
不客气
As powerful as Mr. Ji
像纪总这么厉害
A man with such a good temper
脾气又这么好的人
I don't know in the future
以后也不知道
Who is it cheaper
是便宜了谁了
Beautiful and excellent
漂亮和优秀
It has to be an entry condition
得是入门条件吧
Isn't that a good deal for me
那还不就便宜我了呗
You're real
你是真的
Do you only like to drink American style
只喜欢喝美式吗
Of course
当然
Then why are you today
那你为什么今天
Drink the Aurui white I bought
喝了我买的澳瑞白啊
I'm afraid of waste
我那是怕浪费
Fear of waste
怕浪费
That's my money
那是我的钱
What are you afraid of wasting
你怕浪费什么
Your money. That's my money, too
你的钱那也是我的钱
And now our money
而且现在我们的钱
Is common property
是共有财产
What's more
更何况
You bought it
是你买的
Can that still taste bad
那还能难喝吗
You hurry
你快
Send the milk to Mom
把牛奶给妈送过去吧
I'll go up
我上去
Check customer information
查一下客户资料
Soon
马上就要
Independent development customer
独立开发客户了
Do you have confidence
有信心吗
Even if you have confidence, you won't meet your performance
有信心也不顶业绩呀
Or make a few more phone calls
还是多打几个电话
It's more practical to attract a few customers
拉几个客户比较实在
Can I help you
需要我帮忙吗
Need not
不用
Definitely not use it
坚决不用
The two of us
我们两个
But there's an agreement
可是有协议在身的
We are competitors
我们是竞争对手
I'm not gonna throw in the towel
我不会认输的啊
You don't have to give me a green light
你也不用给我开绿灯
Don't worry
你放心
I will rely on my own strength
我会靠我自己的实力
turned regular
转正的
Okay
行
Then I'll leave you alone
那我就不打扰你了
I'm going to read books too
我也去看书
Done
好了
Didn't you go to read a book
你不是看书去了吗
Why so quickly
怎么这么快
Have you warmed up a glass of milk
给你热了杯牛奶
Thank you
谢谢
I have lost weight recently
我最近减肥
How about skim milk
要不换脱脂牛奶吧
Go ahead
去吧
Go ahead, go ahead
去吧 去吧
This cup is fat-free
这杯就是脱脂的
Drink it while it's hot
趁热喝吧
Then you put it there
那你放那儿吧
I'll drink it in a minute
我一会儿就喝
I want to watch you drink
我想看着你喝
quick
快
Drink it while it's hot
趁热喝
Good
好
Then you go
那 那你去吧
Hiding what
偷藏了什么
Yuheng
昱恒
Xiaoning
筱柠
Are you guys asleep
你们睡了吗
Didn't sleep mom
没睡妈
What's wrong
怎么了
This medicine I took before
我之前吃的这个药啊
Finished eating
吃完了
I didn't find the new one. Where is it?
新的没找到在哪儿
I put it next to the cupboard
我放在柜子旁边了
I'll get it for you
我去给您拿
No, no, no
不用 不用
I can take it myself
我自己拿就行
You guys go to sleep
你们睡吧
Why don't I go
要不我去
I'll go I'll go
我去 我去
Hate
讨厌
Sister Jing
静姐
I contacted
我联系的
Shipyard in Xihai Town
西海镇的造船厂
They want to expand into new business
他们要拓展新的业务
Need a sum of funds
需要一笔资金
The amount is quite large
数额还挺大的
I got in touch with their accountant
我跟他们会计联系好了
Wednesday to
周三到
Do you have anything to tell you
你有什么要嘱咐的吗
That sister wishes you all the best
那姐祝你一切顺利
Their company qualifications are not bad
他们公司资质还不错
I think the loan
我觉得贷款
It should be approved
应该能批下来
If it's done
要是做成了的话
That
那
This customer amount is mine
这个客户数额算我的
Most of the performance is yours
绩效大头都算你的
Book tickets for sister
给姐订票
OK
好嘞
Xihai Town
西海镇
Business trip application
出差申请
Last night
昨天晚上
Why didn't you tell me a word
怎么也没跟我说一声啊
It wasn't decided last night
昨天晚上还没定下来呀
I'll go with Sister Jing
我跟静姐一起去
Five days in total
总共去五天
Mr. Ji, please approve it
请纪总您通过批准一下
Our business trip application
我们的出差申请
Five days
五天
I'm leaving on Wednesday
周三就要走啊
Right
对
Go early
早点去
Do you prepare early
早点做准备吗
Xihai Town
西海镇
It's an island over there
那边是个海岛
It's very windy
风很大
The temperature is relatively low
气温比较低
Remember when I went
记得去的时候
Bring more thick clothes
多带几件厚衣服
As a leader
作为领导
You shouldn't be worried
你不是应该担心
Have I been able to succeed in
我有没有成功地
Customer expansion
拓展客户吗
Work Aspects
工作方面
I'm not too worried
我不太担心
But if you have any
但如果你有任何
I don't understand, I won't
不懂不会的
You can always ask me
可以随时问我
24-hour hotline
二十四小时热线
Open for you
为你开通
Got it
知道了
Go ahead
去吧
Xihai Town
西海镇
Seasickness is much more uncomfortable than motion sickness
晕船可比晕车难受多了
sister
姐
I don't see anything wrong with you
我看你一点事都没有
I'm used to it
我习惯了
Get used to it
习惯了
You used to take a lot of boats
你以前经常坐船啊
Mobile phone
手机
Where are you
到哪儿了
One hour to dock
还有一个小时靠岸
The first day without Ji Yuheng
没有纪昱恒的第一天
Miss him
想他
Fall in love
谈恋爱了
No, no
没 没有啊
Ordinary friends
普通朋友
Sister Jing
静姐
I'm a little dizzy
我真有点头晕
Seasick
晕船了
Let me go down and blow the wind
我下去吹吹风啊
Isn't this just the wind blowing
这不就吹着风呢吗
Hello Xiaoning
喂 筱柠
Did you find any medicine
有找到药吗
Found it
找到了
They've all been eaten
都已经吃了呢
That's good
那就好
I was in a meeting just now
刚刚我在开会
I forgot to tell you in advance
也忘了提前告诉你
This seasickness medicine is put in
这晕船药就放在
It's the outermost part of the bag
包的最外面了
Mr. Ji
纪总
You're so busy
你这么忙了
How can I still take into account
怎么还能顾及到
So many little details
这么多小细节呀
Do you miss that a little bit
那有没有一点点想念
I'm an outstanding one
我这个出类拔萃的
Life Assistant
生活小助手啊
What does laughter mean
笑是什么意思
Is it there or not
那到底是有还是没有啊
Have
有
Okay
行
That's here
那到了
Tell me in time
及时告诉我一声
Rice Go Hotel, right
米果酒店对吗
How do you know
你怎么知道的
Right
对
That small town
那个小镇上
There's only one hotel, right
只有一家酒店对吧
I'm here
我到了呢
Send you WeChat
给你发微信
Good
好
Are you working
你在工作呢吧
Go ahead and get busy
快去忙吧
I hung up
我挂了
You hang up first
你先挂
Bye
拜拜
Mr. Ji
纪总
Just now, the president
刚才行长
I forgot to give you a piece of information
有个资料忘给您了
Thank you for your work
有劳了
Hello
您好
A bottle of milk and a loaf of bread
来瓶牛奶然后一个面包
Ten dollars
十块
Boss, give me a bottle of water
老板来瓶水
Three pieces
三块
So clever Xiaoning
这么巧筱柠
You're here too
你也在这儿
What a coincidence
好巧啊
You won't go to Xihai Town too
不会也去西海镇吧
Yeah
对呀
Let me talk to a client
我来谈个客户
Then your customer is in the manufacturing industry
那你的客户是制造业的
Couldn't they also build ships?
不会也是造船的吧
You guessed it all right
这都被你猜中了
However, the shipyards in the West Sea
不过西海的造船厂
Not much either
也不多
We're not going to the same place, are we
咱俩去的不是同一家吧
The owner of the shop I went to was surnamed Yang
我去的那家老板姓杨
It's really a family
还真是一家呢
But
不过
You may have to waste your trip
你可能要白跑一趟了
This is from me to the development department
这是我来拓展部的
First credit customer
第一个信贷客户
I absolutely wouldn't
我是绝对不会
handed over to others
拱手让人的
Don't let
不用让
Let's each rely on our own skills
咱们各凭本事
Okay
行
I'll see you later
那待会儿见
Sister Jing
静姐
ID card
身份证
And the room card
还有房卡
Sister Na Jing
那 静姐
Sister Xiaoning
筱柠姐
I'm going back to my room first
我先回房间了
Have a good rest
好好休息
She has so many resources
她手里这么多资源
But it happened that I was interested in it
但偏偏看上
You have this client
你手上这个客户
It's interesting
有点意思啊
The contract hasn't been signed yet
合同还没签呢
Not mine either
也不算是我的
Is everyone playing fair
大家公平竞争吗
The mentality is quite good
心态挺好啊
This client is a
这个客户呢是一个
personal investment
个人投资的
No other shareholders are involved
没有其他的股东掺和
Just right for you now
正适合你们现在
Take it to expand customers
拿过来拓展客户
But the company's qualifications
但是公司的资质
Be sure to review it carefully
一定要好好审核
Good
好
Let's be honest
实话实说吧
Is it already
是不是已经
Have you thought of something
想到什么办法了
There is really no way
办法是真没有
But their financial manager said
不过他们财务经理说
You'll have time to see us until the day after tomorrow
大后天才有时间见我们
How about we now
不如我们现在
Just rush into their company
就突击到他们公司
Take a head start
抢个先机
Maybe
说不定
What's the windfall
有什么意外收获呢
Well
嗯
How to do it
办法吧
Not brilliant
不高明
But it's better than
但是胜在
Positive
积极
That is to say
也就是说
Can it be used
能用呗
Manager Tu
涂经理
Unexpectedly
没想到
You guys just arrived and came over
你们刚到就过来了
Look at what I'm preparing here
看我这边准备的
Not quite sufficient either
也不太充分
Manager Liu, you said last time
刘经理您上次说
Enterprises should expand their scale
企业要扩展规模
Probably can provide
大概能提供
Two hundred jobs
两百个就业岗位
I was
我当时
Follow the industry immediately
立马就跟行里
Reported the matter
汇报这件事了
The industry pays special attention to
行里特别重视
I hope I can help you
希望可以帮你们
Solve this urgent need
解决这个燃眉之急
So our manager Rao also came
所以我们饶经理也来了
Hello
您好
If Mr. Yang is here
如果杨总在的话
We can talk
我们可以聊一下
Details of the loan package
贷款方案的细节
If there is any problem
有什么问题的话
Manager Rao can solve it face to face
饶经理可以当面解决
This
这个
Manager Tu
涂经理
Look at it
你看啊
We've been talking for so long
咱们聊了这么久了
You can be considered an acquaintance
也算是熟人了
I'll tell you the truth
我呢就跟您说句实话
Coming and going these two days
这两天来来往往的
They're all from the bank
都是银行的人
Mr. Yang
杨总啊
He thinks it's too troublesome to meet
他又嫌见面太麻烦
It's just a plan
就都只是收个方案
At the end of the day
说到底
I'm just a finance guy
我呢就是个干财务的
What does the boss decide in the end
这老板他最终怎么决定
Is it right
是吧
He wouldn't discuss it with me either
他也不会跟我商量
Then look
那 那 你看
That's our Mr. Yang's
那是我们杨总的
Godson Yang Jie
干儿子杨杰
The girl next to me
旁边那个女孩
I guess it's from which bank
估摸着也是哪家银行的
How about this, Manager Tu
要不这样吧涂经理
Where do I put your plan
我把你们的方案呢
Transfer to Mr. Yang
转交给杨总
If
如果啊
He has the intention
他有意向
I'll contact you then
到时候再联系你
Don't bother, Manager Liu
不用麻烦了刘经理
Our plan
我们这个方案
There are some problems in it
里面有一些问题
Or directly meet Mr. Yang face to face
还是直接当面跟杨总
It would be better to discuss it
讨论一下比较好
Thank you
谢谢您
OK OK OK
也好 也好
That
那
I still have a job
我还有工作
Are you busy
您忙
Good
好
Why don't you give him the plan
为什么不把方案给他
You heard it just now
您刚才也听到了
Recently
最近
There are so many people sending plans
送方案的人那么多
If I give him that plan
要是我把方案给他
I guess Mr. Yang just flipped through it casually
估计杨总就随便翻翻
Doesn't leave any impression
不会留下任何印象吧
Exactly
没错
They receive so many
他们收到这么多的
No decision is made on the plan
方案都不做决定
All you want is
要的就是
Between banks
银行与银行之间
Have a jurisdiction over each other
相互有一个辖制
Finally win one
最后博取一个
The best scheme
最好的方案
So what
所以呢
This trump card in your hand
你手里这张底牌
As long as it doesn't light up
只要不亮
There's still a chance to win
就还有赢的机会
I will definitely find a way
我一定会想办法
To meet Mr. Yang
见杨总一面的
be reasonable
明事理
People's responsibility to understand the law
懂法律的人民责任
Be reasonable and understand the law
明事理 懂法律
Planning to take the public exam
打算考公啊
Mr. Ji
纪总
That is
那个 是
Have this plan
有这个打算
The president knows
行长知道
And always reminds me
还总提醒我
Let me go when I'm not driving
让我在不开车的时候
Pay close attention to study
抓紧学习
Examination in different places
异地考公
It's quite difficult
还挺难的
You have to work at ordinary times
平时你还得工作
It's a lot of pressure, isn't it
压力很大吧
It's really difficult
确实挺难
I just opened the book this evening
这一晚上刚把书翻开呀
Eyelid fight
眼皮子打架
But it's okay
不过没关系
Be able to talk to someone you like
能和喜欢的人
Stay in a city
留在一个城市
Worth
值得
Refuel
加油
Mom
妈
Xiaoheng
小恒
Still busy
还在忙啊
Are you looking for me for something
您找我有事吗
Where today
今天哪
My mother-in-law accompanied me for a stroll
亲家母陪我出去逛了逛
The salesman said
那个售货员说
Talk about this dress
说这个衣服
The version is particularly good
版型特别好
Extremely comfortable to wear
穿着特别舒服
I just bought you one
我就顺手给你买了一件
You bought it for me
您给我买的
Good
好
Thank you Mom
谢谢妈
Try
试试
No
不了
I'll be on my own later
一会儿我自个儿
Go back and try it
回去试吧
You put it on
你穿上
Should Mom have a look
让妈妈看看吗
Good
好
My God
我天
Why is it so much bigger
怎么大这么多
OK
还行
My mother-in-law has reminded me
这亲家母都提醒我了
Say if it will be big
说会不会大了
I was thinking
我是在想
I was thinking about when you went to college
我想着你上大学以后
People have grown so much taller
人长高了这么多
Clothes always need
衣服总归要
One size bigger
大一个尺码的
I didn't expect it to be so much bigger
没想到大这么多
Didn't you say that too
您不也说了吗
This since high school
这个从高中以后
You never bought me any more clothes
您就没再给我买过衣服
This
这个
Also okay
也还行
Can wear
能穿
I'll change one for you tomorrow
我明天去帮你换一件
Take it off
脱下来
I really don't need it
真不用了
No need
不用了
Change one
换一件
You can wear it again later
你以后也可以再穿啊
You
您
If you really go out by yourself
真要是自个儿出去
I'm not at ease either
我也不放心
We won't change it
咱不换了
Okay
行
Then I'll go wash first
那我先去洗漱了
Thank you Mom
谢谢妈
Hello
喂
It's me
是我
Mr. Ji
纪先生
How
怎么
Sounds like you're still busy at work
听起来还在忙工作啊
I'm modifying a loan package
我在修改一个贷款方案
What about you
你呢
What are you doing
你在干吗
I just got out of the shower
我刚洗完澡
What a shame
太可惜了
I don't have this eye blessing
我没有这个眼福
If you give me
你要是给我
Just play the video
打视频就好了
Sounds like
听起来
Rao Jing doesn't seem to be here
饶静似乎不在
Sister Jing went out
静姐出去了
The night in the West Sea is very beautiful
西海的夜色很美的
And there are a lot of small bars
而且还有好多小酒吧
Do you want to video it
那要不要视频一下
Wait for me
你等我一下
What are you laughing about
你笑什么
I laugh at your disheveled clothes
我笑你衣冠不整
improper
不成体统
How are you busy at work
工作忙得怎么样
It went quite smoothly
挺顺利的
Went to their workshop in the afternoon
下午去了他们车间
Loan scheme
贷款方案
Preparations went pretty smoothly, too
也准备得挺顺利的
Strive for an early date
争取早日
Meet them, Mr. Yang
跟他们杨总见面
Sounds like it's going pretty well
听起来进展还算顺利呀
What are you doing
你干什么呢
Pajamas, of course
当然是换睡衣了
Then you change it
那你换吧
I don't watch
我不看
Wait for me
等我一下啊
Done
好了
So it's invisible
这样就看不见了
Why don't you answer?
怎么还不接呀
I, I have something else to do
我 我还有点事
You go to bed early
你早点睡吧
Must be by Ling Weiyi
肯定是被凌惟依
The belt is broken
给带坏了
What a shame
真丢人
mysterious
神神秘秘的
Pajamas
睡衣
What about the dry hair cap
干发帽呢
Hello, hello
喂 你好
Is it Tu Xiaoning
是涂筱柠吗
It's me
是我
Here's your flash
这儿有你的闪送
Come and pick it up
过来取一下吧
I didn't call Flash Delivery
我没有叫闪送啊
It says you
上边写着就是你啊
Xihai Town Miguo Hotel
西海镇米果酒店
Then you put it there
那你放在那儿吧
I'm coming to get it now
我现在过来拿
Thank you
谢谢啊
Okay
行
The first day without Tu Xiaoning
没有涂筱柠的第一天
Miss her
想她
Manager Liu
刘经理
Please
求你了
Why don't you let me meet Mr. Yang
你让我跟杨总见一面吧
After meeting
见了面以后
If he rejects my plan
他要是否定了我的方案
I will never bother him again
我再也不来打扰他
Can you see this Mr. Yang?
这杨总见不见啊
I'm truly saying it doesn't count
我是真说的不算
I'm sorry
对不住了啊
Then make a phone call
那 那打个电话也行啊
One minute
一分钟
I just need a minute
我就只需要一分钟
Hello, how do you do
喂 您好
Is it Mr. Yang
是杨总吗
I'm Tu Xiaoning from Dairui
我是代瑞的涂筱柠
Would you please give me a minute
麻烦您给我一分钟时间
Introduce my own scheme
介绍一下我自己的方案
I'm sorry
不好意思啊
Busy
在忙
Goodbye
再见
Hello
您好
The user you are calling is busy
您所呼叫的用户正忙
Would you please call again later
请您稍后再拨
Sorry
对不起
The user you are calling is busy
您所呼叫的用户正忙
No, no, no, no
不用 不用 不用
You can take it
您拿着吧
Really no need
真不用
It's okay if you take it
您拿着没事
That Mr. Yang
那个 杨总
When do you get off work
什么时候下班啊
Mr. Yang
杨总啊
Isn't this Mr. Yang's car
这不杨总的车吗
Mr. Yang gets off work at this time every day
杨总每天都这个点下班
Thank you
谢谢啊
Be open-minded
想开点
Working as an account manager
干客户经理的
Who hasn't fallen a few stumblings
谁没栽过几个跟头啊
that
那个
Manager Liu thinks I'm pitiful
刘经理看我可怜
And whispered to me
还悄悄跟我说
Tang Yuhui
唐羽卉
I've been in touch with Mr. Yang recently
最近一直在跟杨总联络
It is estimated that these days
估计这几天
It's time to sign the contract
就要签合约了吧
I inquired about it
我打听了一下
Yang Jie, the adopted son of Mr. Yang
那个杨总的干儿子杨杰
It was once Tang Yuhui
是曾经唐羽卉
A friend in the study abroad circle
留学圈的一个朋友
I knew it when I was in the lobby
我在大堂的时候就知道
Resources
资源
More Important Than Effort
比努力更重要
Lost once
输过一次
I didn't expect
我没想到
Lost again this time
这次又输了
But
但是
Losing to God doesn't count as losing
输给老天爷不算输啊
You weren't born in a
你又没有生在一个
You can take it out casually
随随便便就可以拿出
Ten million families filling holes
一千万补窟窿的家庭
No chance
更没有机会
Being in a study abroad circle
身在某个留学圈
To meet someone's godson
去认识某个人的干儿子
This is a random arrangement from God
这是上天随机的安排
It's not your human error
不是你人为的错误
Thank you Sister Jing for comforting me
谢谢静姐安慰我
What about my principles
我的原则呢
That is
就是
Timely stop loss
及时止损
Whether it's your own personal emotions
不管是自己的个人情绪
Or consume in
还是消耗在
Energy in Customers
客户身上的精力
I got it
我知道了
Hello
喂
Sister Jing
静姐
The restaurant next door said
隔壁的餐厅说
Today's seafood is particularly fresh
今天的海鲜特别新鲜
You take Sister Xiaoning with you
你带上筱柠姐
Let's come together
一块过来呗
Xiaoning
筱柠啊
She's already asleep
她已经睡了
Let me go to eat with you
我陪你去吃吧
OK
行啊
I'll see you soon
一会儿见
Have a good rest
好好休息吧
Gone
走了
Xiaoning
筱柠啊
You've been in the business for so long
你在行里工作这么久了
Why can't you see clearly
怎么还看不清
Resources and Connections
资源和人脉
Far more important than diligence
远远比勤奋更重要
I inquired about it
我打听了一下
Yang Jie, the adopted son of Mr. Yang
那个杨总的干儿子杨杰
It was once Tang Yuhui
是曾经唐羽卉
A friend in the study abroad circle
留学圈的一个朋友
I didn't think you liked it
没想到你还喜欢
Eat these little roadside barbecues
吃这些路边小烧烤啊
Sister Jing
静姐
I'm actually
我这个人其实
Very easy to get along with
特别好相处
What about you, if you want to know more about me
你呢只要愿意多了解我
You will find us both
就会发现咱们俩身上
Actually, they have a lot in common
其实有很多共同点
Benefit first
利益至上
unscrupulous
不择手段
These two points are quite like mine
这两点是挺像我的
Don't get me wrong
你别误会啊
These two words are here with me
这两个词在我这儿
Not a derogatory term
可不是贬义词
Sister Jing
静姐
You are in the development department
您在拓展部
But a legend
可是传奇人物
We are here to meet our customers this time
我们这次来见客户
You should also see
您应该也看出
My ability
我的能力了
I have resources
我有资源
You have experience
您有经验
As long as you are willing to take me
只要你愿意带我
Our two powerful alliances
我们两个强强联合
It must be the best result
一定就是最好的结果
Self-righteousness is the most like me
自以为是这点最像我
Come
来
Drink a
喝一个
Sister Jing
静姐
I really want to work with you
我是真心想跟你合作的
I understand
我明白
Originally, I thought
本来我以为
You come and we expand a part
你来我们拓展一部
He came for Ji Yuheng
是奔着纪昱恒来的
But I didn't think I looked down on you
但是没想到我看轻你了
People are self-motivated
人有上进心呢
Not a bad thing
不是什么坏事
But you have to remember
但是你要记住
Not anyone else
不是任何人
Can be dragged here by you
都能被你拖来
As a stepping stone
当垫脚石的
And
还有
Today's meal of wine
今天这顿酒
Sister invited
姐请了
You drink slowly
你慢慢喝
What's wrong with you
你怎么了
sullen
闷闷不乐的
I thought
我本来以为
I'm a lucky man
我是一个挺幸运的人
Successfully passed the full-time examination
顺利通过了转正考试
Found it again smoothly
又顺利找到了
First Customer
第一个客户
The result is still
结果还是
Draw water with a bamboo basket and it's all in vain
竹篮打水一场空啊
Isn't it just a client
不就是个客户吗
At worst, I'll ask my dad to let him
大不了我找我爸让他
I'll give you a small loan of tens of millions
给你贷个小几千万
Let him pull two more of his friends
让他再拉他两个朋友
Maybe hundreds of millions
没准就上亿了
Then let me
那我一下
Wouldn't he become the vice president?
不就成副行长了
I'm walking sideways in Dairy
我在代瑞就横着走
When the time comes, Ji Yuheng and I
到时候我跟纪昱恒
Things about falling in love
谈恋爱的事
Do they have to send red envelopes
是不是他们还要发红包
Give us a celebration
给我们庆祝啊
Of course
那当然
I'll hang up later
我等会儿挂了电话
I'll call my dad
我就给我爸打电话啊
Forget it
算了吧
Don't listen to the wind and rain
你别听风就是雨的了
I'm just kind of
我就是有点
I doubt myself
自我怀疑了
Don't worry
不用担心
It's nothing
这都没什么
Weiyi
惟依
How about this set
这套怎么样
See your uncle appear more dignified
见叔叔显得端庄一点
It's too old-fashioned
太老气了吧
Just like my uncle
跟我舅似的
The blue one just now is better
还是刚那套蓝的好
All right, all right
好了 好了
You guys keep busy
你们忙吧
I'm tired, too. I went back to sleep
我也累了我回去睡了
Xiao Ning, goodbye
筱柠别啊
He wandered around his
他逛他的
Let's talk about us, don't worry about him
咱们聊咱们的不用管他
Make another appointment when you go back
回去再约吧
I hung up
我挂了
Ji Yuheng
纪昱恒
I miss you so much
我很想你
Xiaoning
筱柠
Why are you here
你怎么来了
It's okay
没事了
I'm coming
我来了
How much you have eaten these two days
这两天吃得
It's definitely not to taste
肯定不合口味吧
Look what I brought you
你看我给你带了什么
Egg yolk cake
蛋黄酥
And a lot of snacks
还有好多小零食
And this
还有这个
Home downstairs
家楼下
Seaweed Beckham
海苔小贝
It's all your favorite food
都是你爱吃的
Don't clean up
你别收拾了
Come and sit for a while
过来坐会儿
Come here so late
这么晚了折腾过来
Are you tired
累了吧
Of course I'm not tired
当然不累了
If I don't come
我要是不过来的话
I didn't even know you were alone
我都不知道你一个人
Shed tears secretly
偷偷地掉眼泪
I didn't shed any tears
我可没掉眼泪啊
I did that because I saw you
我那是因为见到你
tears of joy
喜极而泣
Then I'll say it again
那我重新说
After we finish the video
咱们打完视频以后
I suddenly miss you so much
我突然特别想你
I want to see you soon
想快点见到你
Tomorrow is the weekend again
明天又是周末
It's off work today
今天这下了班
I rushed over
我就赶紧赶过来了
Then if you come over
那你要是过来
Mom, what should I do
妈怎么办
It's only been three days since I went downstairs
这才三天没下楼
It's like a reunion after a long absence
整得跟久别重逢似的
The more you jump, the better
越跳越好
in-laws
亲家
Your community
你们小区
It's really lively
可真热闹
I've recovered from my illness later
这回头我病好了
I'm here to play too
我也来这玩儿
Good
好
Play that
玩那个
Top
陀螺啊
Well then
那好那
I'm on the internet later
回头我在网上
I'll buy one for you
给你淘一个
Luminous all night
整一个晚上带夜光的
I'm kidding
我说笑呢
How can I have that energy
我哪有那劲
Can you smoke it
能抽它呀
Where's my water
我水呢
Didn't you take it?
是不是没拿啊
Have a sip of yours
喝口你的来
in-laws
亲家
You guys pick me up
你们接我过来啊
Thank you so much
真是太感谢了
You see what you said
你看你说的
What are these words
这是什么话呀
You stay here
你住过来
Xiaoji
小纪呀
Only then did I have time to find Xiaoning
才有时间去找筱柠
Where's the two of us
咱俩呢
Can sit here too
也能坐在这儿
Speak in a down-to-earth manner
踏踏实实说说话
It's too late for me to be happy
我开心还来不及呢
That's true
说的也是
Then back
那往后呀
Don't you either
你也别
The in-laws and in-laws are shouting that they are divided
亲家亲家的叫着生分了
How many years am I older than you
我比你大几岁
If you don't mind
你要不介意的话
Can I call you sister
我叫你妹妹行吗
That must work
那必须行啊
My sister
我的姐
What's wrong with you this is
你怎么了这是
What do you think is wrong with me
你说我怎么了
Come back tomorrow Come back tomorrow
明天再来 明天再来
Bye
拜拜
This makes you jump
这让你跳
You don't jump
你又不跳
Then I'll
那我就
Then I'll have to dance with someone else
那我就只能跟别人跳了
It's just dancing
跳舞而已呀
Who says I don't jump
谁说我不跳了
Go Sister
走 姐
Let's go square dance
咱俩去跳广场舞去
Go
走
Don't you dance with your father-in-law
你不跟亲家公跳吗
How well he danced just now
他刚才跳得多好啊
Don't care about him
不稀罕他
Let's go
咱俩走
I
我
Let me take pictures of you two
我给你俩拍照片啊
My mother's rhythm
我妈这个节奏啊
It's basically no one
基本上是没有人
Will not be biased
不会被带偏的
Mom is so amazing
妈可真厉害
Such a strong sense of rhythm
节奏感这么强
Actually, my parents
其实爸妈
So that we can get together
为了咱们俩能团聚
Take care of my mom
照顾我妈
I appreciate it
我很感谢
My mom keeps saying
我妈一直都说呢
Want to have a sister
想有个姐妹
She must be particularly happy this time
这回她肯定特别高兴
There is a lot to talk about every day
天天有可多话聊了
Mom went to my house
妈去我家了
Where's Nemo
尼莫呢
Followed by one piece
跟着一块过去了
When we get home
等咱们回到家呀
Pick it up again
再把它接回来
Are you tired
累了吧
Is it because
是不是因为
Tang Yuhui
唐羽卉
I'm going to sign a contract with Mr. Yang
要跟杨总签约了
That's why you're crying
所以才哭鼻子的
You got it
你知道了
And it's not just because of this
也不光是因为这个
I
我
I especially want to work hard
特别想努力
But Mr. Yang doesn't see me
但是杨总他不见我
I'm not convinced
我不服气
But
但是
I
我
Powerless
无能为力
I feel frustrated
我挫败感
It's particularly strong
就特别强
I feel useless
觉得自己很没用
Xiaoning
筱柠
Actually, I have channels
其实我有渠道
Can help you
可以帮你
Contact Mr. Yang
联系上杨总的
Need not
不用
Didn't we agree
咱们不是说好了吗
Don't put the relationships in your life
不要把生活中的关系
Bring to work
带到工作中
Besides, you are
再说你是
The boss of both of us
我们两个人的上司
Even if you don't use your current status
你就算不用现在的身份
Help me get in touch
帮我联系
It's not fair to others either
对别人也不公平呀
Don't worry
你放心吧
I won't give up easily
我不会轻易放弃的
This loan application
这贷款申请
Haven't you reported it yet
不是还没报呢吗
I still have a chance
我还是有机会的
Without violating
在不违反
Under the circumstances of your principles
你原则的情况之下
Where there is any
但凡有任何
Need my help
需要我帮忙的
Be sure to tell me
一定告诉我
Even if
哪怕
It's beating me up
是揍我一顿
Decompression is also fine
解解压也行
You're not a sandbag
你又不是沙包
How can I beat you
我哪舍得打你呀
Are the chest muscles trained for nothing
胸肌是白练的吗
Try
试试
I can't bear to part with it
我可舍不得
Teacher Ji's figure
纪老师的身材
Still really good
还是真不错呀
You delivered this to your door yourself
这是你自己送上门的啊
Rao Jing
饶静
Hello Sister Jing
喂 静姐
What's wrong with your voice
你声音怎么了
Are you dumb
哑了吗
I don't have a voice
我声音 没有啊
What's wrong
怎么了
No, what time is it
不是这都几点了
Where are you
你人呢
You wouldn't
你不会
You're not going to block Mr. Yang again, are you
你不会又去堵杨总了吧
No no
没 没有
Just jump into the sea if you don't think about it
没有想不开跳海就行
Will you come back in the evening
你晚上还回来吗
I'll lock the door if you don't come back
你不回来我锁门了
return
回
I'll be right back
我马上回
Hang up
挂了
Come back soon
快回吧
This Tang Yuhui is really
这个唐羽卉也真是
Let a leader as big as me
放着我这么大个领导
Invisible
看不见
Have to get from the bank again
非得再从银行
Move her over and sign a guy
给她搬过来一个人签字
Who
谁呀
Who else could there be
还能有谁啊
The one I'm most annoying with
我最烦的那个
Brother Zhao
小赵哥呀
Not important
不重要
Let me tell you, Xiao Tu
我跟你说小涂
Doing marketing
做营销的
If only brute force is used
如果只使用蛮力的话
Then you will die of exhaustion
那你一定会累死在
In one's own persistence
自己的坚持里
What about the good client
好的客户呢
Everyone wants to rob it
谁都想抢
If the person you want to see
如果你想见的那个人
Can't see
见不到
You have to find a way
你就要想办法
Let that person come to see you
让那个人来见你
Let him come to see me
让他来见我
Right
对
Let him come to see you
让他来见你
Remember to turn off the lights later
一会儿记得关灯啊
Good
好
fishing rod
鱼竿
Are you sleeping
睡了吗
Make an appointment for your time tomorrow
预约你明天的时间
Be with you at any time
随时奉陪
Please come out quickly
你快一点出来吧
Hurry up
快点
Come on, come on, come on
快点 快点 快点
Thank you
谢谢
You're welcome
不客气
I'll do it
我来
This pole is so heavy
这个竿好沉啊
The wind and waves of sea fishing are too big
海钓的风浪太大了
The water is also deep
水也深
So the rod has to be heavier
所以竿必须要重一些
There is also the most important thing
另外还有一个最重要的
You can't use those for fishing bait
鱼饵不能用那些
Earthworms and bugs
蚯蚓和小虫子
Need to use this specially made
需要用这种专门制作的
Choose one
选一个
What's wrong
怎么了
It's okay
没事
Just pricked it
就扎了一下
Let me see
我看看
It's okay
没事
Why are you so careless
怎么这么不小心
I'm not that delicate
我没那么娇气
You still carry this with you
你还随身带着这个呀
Of course
当然了
The fins are very hard
鱼鳍是很硬的
Especially afraid that you will be pricked
特别怕你被扎到
But I didn't expect
可是没想到
The hook scraped you
鱼钩把你给刮到了
Come
来
So be careful
所以说千万要小心一点
I'm not willing to let you get hurt
我可不舍得你受伤的
Blame me too
也怪我
Should have warned you in advance
刚刚应该提前提醒你的
Good night
晚安